听力考试正式开始。
请看听力部分第一节。
第一节。
听下面五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题。
从题中所给的
three A, B, and Read
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听完每段对话后，你都。
都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。
in paper. Excuse me, can you tell me how much the shirt is?
你将听到以下内容。
Yes, it's 9.15.
你将有五秒钟的时间。
将正确答案标在试卷上。
衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士，所以你选择
项，并将其标在试卷上。
现在你有五秒钟的时间
阅读第。
第一小题的有关内容。
I was in Mallorca last week.
Oh, what were you doing there?
My best friend worked there, and I went to visit her.
It was a good chance to practice my Spanish.
Ruth, I've got this terrible cold, and I have to see a doctor.
I'm afraid I can't go to the class.
Could you help me hand in my lab report to Dr.
Davidson? Sure, no problem.
Just take care of yourself, and don't worry about the class.
Marie, if no one takes care of your children while you're away, Jennifer and I will
be glad to have them stay with us.
That's very kind of you.
But they've already left for their grandmas.
You know, Susie lives close by.
Hurry up with your food, Sally.
They say there's a big storm coming.
We'd better get home before that.
Okay, I'm done.
Let's get back to the car.
Could you carry these shopping bags?
Oh, sure. We deep -fried fish three days ago in the kitchen, but the unpleasant
smell stays. There's a method you can try.
Every time you make coffee, dry the leftover coffee grounds and keep them in small
bowls. Then place the bowls in the kitchen.
第一节。
节到此结束。
第二节，听下面五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
three A, B, and lasts
三个选项中。
选出最佳选项。
听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间
阅读各个小题，每小题
五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七两个小题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两。
两个小题。
Are you a football fan, Gomez?
Yes, I go to the stadium whenever there's a good game, and if I can't get a ticket,
I watch the game on TV.
That way, they are less exciting, though.
Is the ticket expensive?
It depends. It usually costs about twenty to fifty dollars.
Last time, I paid twenty -five.
That's not very expensive.
Maybe we can go together sometime.
Great! It'll be more fun to watch the game with a friend.
Are you a football fan, Gomez?
Yes, I go to the stadium whenever there's a good game, and if I can't get a ticket,
I watch the game on TV.
That way, they are less exciting, though.
Is the ticket expensive?
It depends. It usually costs about twenty to fifty dollars.
Last time, I paid twenty -five.
That's not very expensive.
Maybe we can go together sometime.
Great! It'll be more fun to watch the game with a friend.
听下面一段对话，回答第八至第十
三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
I took a walk by myself.
You just kept walking and walking for four hours?
Actually, it's not so boring.
Walking in the woods is a grand adventure.
Your feet can take you to the most amazing places.
What did you do in the woods?
I smelled the flowers, looked at the birds, and yeah, I picked many tree leaves.
I will make bookmarks with them.
Look! Aren't they beautiful?
Then I met Bob at the lake.
He was fishing while his kids were having a swim.
Did you talk to him?
No. I walked on and took a lot of pictures.
There's just so much out there to see.
You were out the whole afternoon, Alex.
What did you do?
I took a walk by myself.
You just kept walking and walking for four hours?
Actually, it's not so boring.
Walking in the woods is a grand adventure.
Your feet can take you to the most amazing places.
What did you do in the woods?
I smelled the flowers, looked at the birds, and yeah, I picked many tree leaves.
I will make bookmarks with them.
Look! Aren't they beautiful?
Then I met Bob at the lake.
He was fishing while his kids were having a swim.
Did you talk to him?
No. I walked on and took a lot of There's just so much out there to see.
听下面一段对话，回答第十一至第十三
三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
David, how was your holiday?
Great! I climbed Mount Fuji.
It was really beautiful.
Now I can check one more thing off my list.
Your list? Yes.
When I was 12, I made a list of things I wanted to do some day.
That's interesting. How many of the things on your list have you done so far?
Almost half. I have pictures.
Would you like to see them?
Yes, sure. Here I am on top of Mount Fuji.
And here I am in a hot air balloon.
When did you do that?
I've always wanted to go up in a hot air balloon.
It was two years ago, in August, in
What are your plans for the next holiday?
I'm thinking of deep sea diving in Australia.
Do you have any other suggestions?
You really ought to take a boat down the Amazon.
You'll see a of interesting animals and beautiful trees.
It's one of the best places I've been to.
Okay. I'll put it on my list.
David, how was your holiday?
Great! I climbed Mount Fuji.
It was really beautiful.
Now I can check one more thing off my list.
Your list? Yes.
When I was 12, I made a list of things I wanted to do some day.
That's interesting.
How many of the things on your list have you done so far?
Almost half. I have pictures.
Would you like to see them?
Yes, sure. Here I am on top of Mount Fuji.
And here I am in a hot air balloon.
When did you do that?
I've always wanted to go up in a hot air balloon.
What are your plans for the next holiday?
I'm thinking of deep sea diving in Australia.
Do you have any other suggestions?
You really ought to take a boat down the Amazon.
You'll see a lot of interesting animals and beautiful trees.
It's one of the best places I've been to.
Okay. I'll put it on my list.
听下面一段对话，回答第十四至第十七
四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Okay. Hello, Michael.
Hi, Sarah. Are you attending the conference tomorrow morning at the Shelton Hotel?
Yes. Are you?
Yeah, but when I arrived home five minutes ago, I found that my car wouldn't start.
And John is in Brighton on business.
Do you know what's wrong with the car?
I'm not exactly sure.
I think there's a problem with the engine.
I wonder if you could give me a ride to the hotel tomorrow morning.
Sure. When shall I be at your place?
Well, what about eight o From my place to Shelton, we have to drive through the
quarters, so we'd better leave early to avoid the traffic.
Okay, no problem.
It takes 20 minutes to reach your place, so I'll set off at 7.40.
By the way, do you also need me to drive you home tomorrow afternoon?
No. John will be back then, and he'll get me home.
Thank you, Michael.
That's okay. See you tomorrow.
Hello, Michael. Hi, Sarah.
Are you attending the conference tomorrow morning at the Shelton Hotel?
Yes. Are you?
Yeah, but when I arrived home five minutes ago, I found that my car wouldn't start.
And John is in Brighton on business.
Do you know what's wrong with the car?
I'm not exactly sure.
I think there's a problem with the engine.
I wonder if you could give me a ride to the hotel tomorrow morning.
Sure. When shall I be at your place?
Well, what about eight o From my place to Shelton, we have to drive through the
quarters, so we'd better leave early to avoid the traffic.
Okay, no problem.
It takes twenty minutes to reach your place, so I'll set off at 7.40.
By the way, do you also need me to drive you home tomorrow afternoon?
No. John will be back then, and he'll get me home.
Thank you, Michael.
That's okay. See you tomorrow.
Thank you. Hello everyone.
听下面一段独白。
回答第十八至。
第二十三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Today I'll talk about how to improve your pronunciation.
Language researchers say pronunciation and fluency are the biggest barriers,
followed by grammar, in effective spoken English.
However, most people don't regard pronunciation as a very important part of
communication skills. They're more focused on vocabulary.
One reason is that most people are not even aware of their mispronunciations.
So it's important to first find out the words you mispronounce.
You should listen to experts.
By experts, I mean those who are less likely to make pronunciation mistakes.
When listening to pay attention to words that sound strange.
because you pronounce the same words differently.
When you come across such words, check a dictionary to confirm their exact
pronunciations. You can also search for difficult -to -pronounce words and names and
make a list of The last suggestion is to read aloud.
Now you've got the correct pronunciations of the words.
It's time to practice reading them every day.
Hello, everyone. Today I'll talk about how to improve your pronunciation.
Language researchers say pronunciation and fluency are the biggest barriers,
followed by grammar,
in effective spoken English.
However, most people don't regard pronunciation as a very important part of
communication skills.
They're more focused on vocabulary.
One reason is that most people are not even aware of their mispronunciations.
So, it's important to first find out the words you mispronounce.
You should listen to experts.
By experts, I mean those who are less likely to make pronunciation mistakes.
When listening to pay attention to words that sound strange.
Strange because you pronounce the same words differently.
When you come across such words, check a dictionary to confirm their exact
pronunciations. You can also search for difficult -to -pronounce words and names and
make a list of The last suggestion is to read aloud.
Now you've got the correct pronunciations of the words.
It's time to practice reading them every day.
第二。
别到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案
转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you for watching!
you you you
听力部分到此结束。